Finding Aid for Robert C. Metcalf papers, 1950-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Project Files
  - Projects by Job Number
    - Job No. 109-83,Professors John H. and Maurita Holland 3800 W. Huron River Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1983
      - Architectural Drawings (Box 8)
        (see Job 84-64, Holland)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 110-83, Professor and Mrs. Charles W. Phillips, 912 Aberdeen Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1983
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
        (see Job 15-55, Phillips)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 111-85, Mr. Karl Kienholz, Ann Arbor, MI 1985
      - Architectural Drawings, 2 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 112-86, Professor and Mrs. Eric Stein 2649 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI, 1986
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
        (see Job 46-59, Peter)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 113-88, Professor and Mrs. Lawrence S. Bartell, 381 Riverview Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1988
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 12x17.5 & 49 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Graphics File (Box 8)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 114-88, Drs. Ian and Millicent Higgins, 252 Indian River Place, Ann Arbor, MI 1988
      - Architectural Drawings, see Job 96-67, Higgins (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
        (see Job 96-67, Higgins)
    - Job No. 115-88, Mr. and Mrs. Merlin T. Ferriell 2065 Nayland Road, Columbus, OH, 1988
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 18x12, 1 22x16, 1 24x16, 1 23x15, & 10 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Job No. 117-89, Dr. David Fox and Dr. Paula Bockenstedt, 200 Barton North Drive, Barton Hills, MI 1989
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 12x16.5, 1 24x13, 1 24x14, 39 24x18, 19 34x22, & 2 34x24-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 9)
      - Client File, 4 folders (Box 8)
      - Graphics File (Box 8)
      - Slides (Box 9)
        (see Box 12, slide boxes 5 & 9)
    - Job No. 118-89, Professor Elmer Gilbert and Professor Lois Verbrugge (II) 4875 Crystal Drive, Beulah, MI, 1989
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 17x12, 1 22x18, 1 22x11, 1 23x18, & 25 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum and paper; studies, rendering, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
      - Graphics File (Box 8)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 119-89, Mr. and Mrs. Don W. Robinson 1045 Chestnut Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1989
      - Architectural Drawings, 7 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections (Box 8)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 120-91, Mr. and Mrs. John H. Holland (II), Lot 7, Old Deerfield-Michigan Shores, MI 1991
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x16 & 46 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Graphics File (Box 8)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide box 5)
    - Job No. 121-91, Professor and Mrs. Ed Yao 2935 Hickory Lane, Ann Arbor, MI, 1991
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 8 .5x11 & 28 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
        (see also Job 52-59, Moyer)
      - Client File (Box 8)
      - Graphics File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 122-92, Attorney and Mrs. John R. Laird (III) 3150 Hunting Valley Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1992
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
        (see Job 105-74, Laird (II)
      - Client File (Box 8)
        see Job 105-74, Laird (II))
    - Job No. Misc 1992 Mr. Howard Gutstein, 6800 Park Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1992
      (modifications not built)
      - Architectural Drawings, 7 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. Misc. 1992 Mr. and Mrs. Harold A. Jahnke, 2121 Tuomy Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1992
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 12x11, 1 12x12, 1 12.5x12, 1 13x12, 4 14x12, 1 14.5 x12, 2 15x12, 2 15 .5x12, 1 16.5x12, 3 18x12, & 5 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 123-93, Dr. Stanley Watson and Dr. Huda Akil 3351 Windshadow Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1992
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
        (see Job 108-80, Watson/Akil)
      - Client File (Box 8)
        (see Job108-80, Watson/Akil)
    - Job No. Misc. 1993 Dr. and Mrs. Tom Saladin, 11716 Algonquin Drive, Portage Lake, Hamburg, MI, 1993
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 17x12, 1 18x12, & 5 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; sketches and plans (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 124-94, Messrs. Thomas Hitchman and Keith Hewitt 5275 N. Adams Road, Bloomfield Township, MI, 1994
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
        (see Job 139-01, Hitchman/Hewitt)
      - Client File (Box 8)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 125-95, Mr. John Bareham, 309 River View Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1995
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
        (see Job 145-03, Bareham)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 126-95, Ms. Ruth Siegel, 19 Heatheridge Street, Ann Arbor, MI 1995
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide box 9)
    - Job No. 127-95, Mr. and Mrs. Bob DeLosh 4040 E. Huron River Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1995
      - Architectural Drawings, 23 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 128-96, Oak Valley Dental Associates 2420 Oak Valley Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1996 (Map-case 10)
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 17x12, 2 21.5x12, 1 21.5x13, 2 22.5x12, 1 24x12, 1 24x13, 2 24x14, 1 24x15, 65 24x18, 1 31x12, & 21 36x24-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on tracing paper, pencil on vellum, colored pencil on paper; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Box 9)
      - Client File, 6 folders (Box 9)
      - Graphics File (Box 9)
      - Presentation Boards, 1 23.5x18 & 1 24x20-inch boards; outsized (Map-case 15)
    - Job No. 129-96, Professor and Mrs. Elliot Valenstein, 260 Indian River Place, Ann Arbor, MI 1996
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 10)
        (see Job 86-64, Olds)
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 130-96, Mr. and Mrs. Lawrence W. Waggoner 1119 Chestnut Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1996
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 10)
        (see Job No. 23-56, Duckek (I))
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 131-97, Dr. and Mrs. Vigen Darian 1329 Glendaloch Circle, Ann Arbor, MI, 1997
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 8.5 x11, 2 12x9, 1 16x12, & 39 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum and paper; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 10)
        (see also Job No. 85-64, Mann)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Graphics File (Box 9)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
    - Job No. 132-97, Professor Peter Hinman & Dr. Elizabeth Young 1075 Chestnut Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1997
      - Architectural Drawings (Box 9)
        (see Job 64-60, Elliott)
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 133-98, Mr. and Mrs. Jamie Seguino 2255 Glendaloch Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1998
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 1)
        (see Job 8-55, Moore)
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 134-99, Professors John H. and Maurita Holland 3800 W Huron River Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1999
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 7)
      - Presentation Boards (Map-case 13)
    - Job No. 135-99, Mr. and Mrs. Robert Eckstein, 15 Harvard Place, Ann Arbor, MI 1999
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 2)
        (see Job 21-56, Gerard)
      - Client File (see Job 21-56, Gerard) (Box 2)
    - Job No. 136-99, Mr. Paul C. McCoy and Ms. Shelley Steele 1109 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI, 1999
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 18x12, 1 21x12, 1 23x18, & 27 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Box 2)
        (see also Job 28-57, Magee)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 137-99, Mr. Peter Newhouse, 715 Spring Valley, Barton Hills, MI 1999
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 3)
        (see Job 39-58, Pryor)
      - Client File (Box 3)
    - Job No. 138-99, Ann Arbor Airport Old Terminal Building, Ann Arbor Municipal Airport, 801 Airport Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1999
      - Architectural Drawings, 8 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 10)
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. Misc. 2000 Dr. and Mrs. Chung Owyang, 3600 Fox Hunt Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 2000
      - Architectural Drawings, 7 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans & elevations (Map-case 10)
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 139-01, Messrs. Thomas Hitchman and Keith Hewitt 5275 N. Adams Road, Bloomfield Hills, MI, 2001
      - Architectural Drawings for Job Nos. 139-01 & 124-94, 32 24x18 & 3 48x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 10)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Graphics File (Box 9)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 140-01, Dr. Stanley Watson and Dr. Huda Akil 3351 Windshadow Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 2001
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 141-02, Professor Elmer Gilbert and Professor Lois Verbrugge (II) 2659 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI, 2002
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 8)
        (see Job 94-66, Gilbert)
      - Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. 142-02, Professor Jessy W. Grizzle & Dr. Laurie McCauley 2424 Londonderry Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 2002
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 7)
        (see Job No. 87-65, Leabo)
      - Client File, see Job No. 87-65, Leabo (Box 5)
    - Job No. 143-02, Mr. and Mrs. Evan Cohen/ Dr. and Mrs. Barry Siegel 1041 Belmont Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 2002
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 2)
        (see Job 26-56, Woods)
      - Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 144-02, Ms. Sylvia Hurtado 3130 Dolph Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 2002
      (see also Job No. 47-59, Carr)
      - Architectural Drawings, 9 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 145-03, Mr. and Mrs. John Bareham, 309 Riverview Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 2003
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 125-95 & 145-03, 1 18x12, 1 20x18, & 74 24-18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 10)
      - Client File for Job 125-95 (Box 9)
      - Client File for Job 145-03, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Graphics File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 146-03, Dr. Stanley Watson and Dr. Huda Akil 3351 Windshadow Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 2003
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 8)
    - Job No. 147-03, Dr. and Mrs. Paul Berkowitz 3005 Exmoor Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 2003
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 11.5x8.5, 1 12x9.5, 1 12x10, 1 12x12, 1 15.5x12, 1 16.5x12, 1 18x12, & 22 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 10)
      - Client File (Box 9)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
    - Job No. 148-03, Mr. Jessy W. Grizzle & Ms. Laurie McCauley, 2424 Londonderry Road, Ann Arbor, MI 2002
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 10)
        (see Jobs 142-02 Grizzle/McCauley & 87-65, Leabo)
      - Client File (Box 9)
    - Job No. 149-05, Reza Morshidi and Setareh Moazzami, 119 Dixboro Road, Ann Arbor, MI 2005
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 8.5x11, 1 9x12, 1 11x8.5, 1 11x9, 1 11.5 x 9.5, 1 12x10, & 60 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 10)
        (see also Job 51-59, Chen)
      - Client File (Box 9)
        (folders 1-5)
      - Client File (Box 10)
        (continued, folders 6-12)
      - Graphics File (Box 10)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
    - Job No. 150-07, Mr. and Mrs. Dave Deromedi (Brigham), 819 Avon Road, Ann Arbor, MI 2007
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 8.5x11, 4 22x12, 13 24x18, 1 34x22; pencil on paper & vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 10)
      - Client File (Box 10)
    - Job No. 151-08, Professor John H. Holland 3800 W. Huron River Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 2008
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 7)
      - Client File (Box 5)
  - Projects without Job Numbers
    - Aris (GBB Wilcox House) (Box 10)
    - Beth Israel Community Center, Ann Arbor, MI 1963 (Box 10)
    - Blackett, Mr. O.W., 691 Spring Valley Drive, Barton Hills, MI 1959 (Box 10)
    - Chambers, Mr. David, 1126 Ferdon Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1972 (Box 10)
    - Daniels, Mr. Jim, Cavanaugh Lake, MI (Box 10)
    - Davey, Mr. Winthrop N., 495 Hillspur Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1960 (Box 10)
    - Divine Shepherd Lutheran Church, 1624 Winsted Boulevard, Ann Arbor, MI 1965 (Box 10)
    - Dwight, Dr. and Mrs. Wendell H., 405 N. Putman Street, Williamston, MI 1972 (Box 10)
    - Eaton, Professor Leonard, Hillwood Subdivision, Ann Arbor 1977 (Box 10)
    - Elementary School, Ann Arbor Public Schools, Ann Arbor, MI 1960 (Box 10)
    - First Brethren Church, Canton, OH 1959 (Box 10)
    - Griesinger, Mr. and Mrs. Frank, 837 East Comstock, Owosso, MI 1952 (Box 10)
    - Handy, Mr. and Mrs. James, Ann Arbor 1949 (Box 10)
    - Harris, Mr. and Mrs. William P., 855 Ellair Place, Grosse Pointe, MI 1971 (Box 10)
    - Holden, Mrs. Jackie, Ann Arbor, MI 1971 (Box 10)
    - Hubbard, Dr., Ann Arbor, MI 1959 (Box 10)
    - Huron Valley Girl Scout Council, Campsite, Livingston County, MI 1962 (Box 10)
    - Kulitz, Miss and Mr. Martin, Gilbert Lake, MI (Box 10)
    - Kurkjian, Mr. John R. and Mr. Fisher, Ann Arbor, MI (Box 10)
    - Lingon, Dr. John, 2126 Mershon Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1981 (Box 10)
    - Loch Alpine Golf and Swim Club, Webster Golflands, Inc., Ann Arbor, MI 1962 (Box 10)
    - Love, Mr. Gilbert R., 811 Mount Vernon Street, Ann Arbor, MI 1960 (Box 10)
    - Malvin, Mr. Richard, 2707 Englave Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 2002 (Box 10)
    - Michener, Mr. Ralph, 2115 Devonshire Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1987 (Box 10)
    - Phi Sigma Sigma Sorority, Ann Arbor, MI 1961 (Box 10)
    - Planert, Ingrid, 2065 Day Street, Ann Arbor, MI 2002 (Box 10)
    - Potters Guild, Ann Arbor 1962 (Box 10)
    - Price, Mr. Gorton F., Lots 4 & 5 "Woodlawn Farms," Adrian, MI 1954 (Box 10)
    - St. Clare's Episcopal Mission, Mission of St. Clare of Assisi, Ann Arbor, MI 1965 (Box 10)
    - Schaffer, Mr. and Mrs. Karl, 1251 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI 2001 (Box 10)
    - Shapiro, Professor Harold T., 2025 Hill Street, Ann Arbor, MI 1971 (Box 10)
    - Sharp, 440 S. Main Street, Ann Arbor, MI 1961 (Box 10)
    - Spindler, Dr. A.C., 1545 Sheridan Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1972 (Box 10)
    - Stahl, Mr. Irving N., 18098 Littlefield Street, Detroit, MI 1965 (Box 10)
    - Stern, Dr. Alexandra, Ann Arbor, MI 2002 (Box 10)
    - Uete, Mr. and Mrs. Hiro, 320 Riverview Drive, Ann Arbor, MI (Box 10)
    - Weddige, Professor Emil, 870 Stein Road, Ann Arbor, MI 2000 (Box 10)
    - Weinstein, Mr. and Mrs. Michael 2930 Hickory Lane, Ann Arbor, MI, 1988 (Box 10)
- General Files
  Materials in the General Files series, 1950-2008 (1.0 linear feet), include news clippings on Metcalf's architectural projects, profiles of Metcalf, and articles about other notable Michigan architects. Included in the series are six folders of teaching materials used by Metcalf in the real estate building course he taught for the University of Michigan Extension Service. The series also contains back issues of Architrave by the American Institute of Architects (AIA) Huron Valley and the AIA Michigan Bulletin, a folder of client specifications, and the portfolio for Metcalf's AIA Fellowship Award application.
  - "Bettie's Personal Collection of our Work," circa 1955-1978 (Box 10)
  - Buildings by Michigan Architects in Michigan circa 1965 (Box 10)
  - Buildings by Michigan Architects in Other States circa 1965 (Box 10)
  - Clients 1950-2001 (Box 10)
  - Client Specifications circa 1953-1965 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous circa 1955-1975 (Box 10)
  - Newsletters
    - Architrave AIA Huron Valley, circa 2000-2006 (Box 10)
    - Bulletin, AIA Michigan, circa 1994-2007 (Box 10)
  - News clippings, 4 folders (Box 11)
    - 1950-1970 (Box 11)
    - 1970-1990 (Box 11)
    - 1990-2008 (Box 11)
    - Undated (Box 11)
  - Portfolio for AIA Fellowship Award circa 1970 (Box 11)
    (includes black and white photographs)
  - Study Guide History of Architecture circa 1950, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Teaching Materials
    - 1959 (Box 11)
    - 1962 (Box 11)
    - 1963 (Box 11)
    - 1965 (Box 11)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 11)
    - 1972 (Box 11)
  - Work Featured in Architectural Journals and Other Publications circa 1955-2007 (Box 11)
- Audio Visual Materials
  The Audio Visual series, 1950-2005 (1.5 linear feet), contains photographic prints, negatives, slides, and photographs on compact disc of Metcalf, his colleagues, and his architectural projects. The series is divided into two subseries: Photographs and Negatives, and Slides.
  - Photographs and Negatives
    The Photographs and Negatives subseries includes prints, negatives, and photographs of Metcalf houses on eleven compact discs. Many of the images were taken by Fred Golden whom Metcalf commissioned to photograph his buildings.
    - Photographic Prints (Box 11)
    - Photographs on CD of select Metcalf houses, 11 optical disks CDs
      - Compact Disc 1
        - Job 84-64, Holland (I) (Box 11)
        - Job 94-66, Gilbert (I) (Box 11)
      - Compact Disc 2
        - Job 31-57, Fajans (Box 11)
        - Job 96-67, Higgins (Box 11)
        - Job 100-68, Steiner (Box 11)
        - Job 107-78, Claeys (Box 11)
      - Compact Disc 3
        - Job 76-62, Van Boven (Box 11)
      - Compact Discs 4 & 5
        - Job 108-80, Watson/Akil (Box 11)
      - Compact Disc 6
        - Job 147-03, Berkowitz (Box 11)
      - Compact Disc 7
        - Job 131-97, Darian (Box 11)
      - Compact Disc 8
        - Job 94-66, Gilbert (I) (Box 11)
      - Compact Disc 9
        - Job 149-05, Morshidi / Moazzami (Box 11)
      - Compact Discs 10 & 11
        - Job 90-65, Miller (Box 11)
    - 35mm Negatives of photographs of the work of the office of Robert C. Metcalf, 3 negatives (Box 11)
  - Slides
    The Slides subseries includes two slide boxes of images documenting the construction and renovation of the Metcalf house, as well as nine additional slide boxes of images of completed and under-construction Metcalf houses. The slides of Metcalf's projects are organized by project number and name. The Slides subseries also includes slides Metcalf took of buildings in Ann Arbor, Boston, Chicago, Cleveland, Dallas, Detroit, Grand Rapids, Kansas City, New York City, Oberlin, Phoenix, Philadelphia, Pittsburgh, San Antonio, Syracuse, and Washington, D.C., as well as slides he used in teaching construction at the University of Michigan.
    - General Slides, 4 boxes
      - Chicago & West (Box 11)
      - University of Michigan/ Ann Arbor/ Detroit/ Michigan (Box 11)
      - East (Box 11)
      - >Slides Used in Teaching Construction (Box 12)
    - Metcalf Houses, 11 boxes
      (These slides are also listed in the Project Files series)
      - Slide Box 0, House of Robert C. and Bettie J. Metcalf
        - 1950s (Box 12)
        - 1960s (Box 12)
        - 1970s (Box 12)
        - 1980s (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
      - Slide Box 00, House of Robert C. and Bettie J. Metcalf, Construction
        - 1952 (Box 12)
        - c1970 (Box 12)
        - 1972 (Box 12)
        - 1981 (Box 12)
        - 1988 (Box 12)
        - 1989 (Box 12)
        - Duplicate Slides of Construction (Box 12)
        - Weathering Issues Over the Years (Box 12)
      - Slide Box 1 (Metcalf Houses)
        - Job Misc. 1950 Brechbuhler (Box 12)
        - Job 1-53, Crane (Box 12)
        - Job 2-54, Service (Box 12)
        - Job 3-54, Elving (Box 12)
        - Job 4-54, Dennison (Box 12)
        - Job 5-54, Stockon (Box 12)
        - Slide Box 12 (cont.) (Box 12)
        - Job 6-54, B. Williams (Box 12)
        - Job 7-55, Forsythe (Box 12)
        - Job 8-55, Moore (Box 12)
        - Job 9-55, Jones (Box 12)
        - Job 10-55, Wollam Restaurant (Box 12)
        - Job 12-55, Gamma Phi Beta (Box 12)
        - Job 13-55, Hodges (Box 12)
        - Job 15-55, Phillips (Box 12)
        - Job 20-56, Reynolds (Box 12)
        - Job 23-56, Duckek (I) (Box 12)
        - Job 26-56, Woods (Box 12)
        - Job 27-56, Patterson (Box 12)
        - Job 28-57, Magee (Box 12)
        - Job 31-57, Fajans (Box 12)
        - Job 32-57, Gottlieb (Box 12)
        - Job 33-57, Botch (Box 12)
        - Job 35-57, Church of the Good Shepherd (Box 12)
        - Job 36-57, Sahlins (Box 12)
        - Job 37-58, Harvey (Box 12)
        - Job 39-58, Pryor (Box 12)
        - Job 40-58, Campbell (Box 12)
        - Job 41-58, Titiev (Box 12)
      - Slide Box 2 (Metcalf Houses)
        - Job 42-58, Les Strang (Box 12)
        - Job 43-58, Brown (Box 12)
        - Job 44-58, West Park Shelter (Box 12)
        - Job 45-59, Dingman (Box 12)
        - Job 46-59, Peter (Box 12)
        - Job 48-59, Grimord (Box 12)
        - Job 49-59, Busard (Box 12)
        - Job 50-59, St. Andrew's United Church of Christ (Box 12)
        - Job 51-59, Chen (Box 12)
        - Job 52-59, Moyer (Box 12)
        - Job 54-60, Emerick (Box 12)
        - Job 59-60, Mulchahey (Box 12)
        - Job 60-60, Greenbaum (Box 12)
        - Job 64-60, Elliott (Box 12)
        - Job 65-60, Case (Box 12)
        - Job 67-61, Breed (Box 12)
        - Job 69-61, Spencer (Box 12)
        - Job 70-61, Ogden (Box 12)
        - Job 71-61, Fuller (Box 12)
        - Job 72-61, Davidson/Sherwin (Box 12)
        - Job Misc. 1961 Likert (Box 12)
        - Job Misc. 1961 Spurr (Box 12)
        - Job 73-62, Island Park Shelter (Box 12)
        - Job 74-62, Duckek (II) (Box 12)
        - Job 75-62, Root (Box 12)
        - Job 76-62, Van Boven (Box 12)
        - Job 78-62, Krigbaum (Box 12)
        - Job 79-63, BBON Venture (Box 12)
      - Slide Box 3 (Metcalf Houses)
        - Job 81-63, Heywood (Box 12)
        - Job 82-63, Laird (I) (Box 12)
        - Job 83-64, Swartz (Box 12)
        - Job 85-64, Mann (Box 12)
        - Job 86-64, Olds (Box 12)
        - Job 87-65, Leabo (Box 12)
        - Job 88-65, Eberbach (Box 12)
        - Job 90-65, Miller (Box 12)
        - Job 91-65, Hutt (Box 12)
        - Job 92-66, K. Siegel (Box 12)
        - Job 93-66, Swanson (Box 12)
        - Job 94-66, Gilbert (Box 12)
        - Job Misc. 1966 St. Luke's Lutheran Church (Box 12)
        - Job 95-67, Metcalf Office (Box 12)
        - Job 96-67, Higgins (Box 12)
        - Job Misc. 1967 Lewis (Box 12)
        - Job 98-68, Bentley Park Shelter (Box 12)
        - Job 101-69, Nu Sigma Nu (Box 12)
      - Slide Box 4 (Metcalf Houses)
        - Job 105-74, Laird (II) (Box 12)
        - Job 106-75, Huebner (Box 12)
        - Job 107-78, Claeys (Box 12)
        - Job 108-80, Watson/Akil (Box 12)
        - Job 113-88, Bartell (Box 12)
        - Job 124-94, Hitchman/Hewitt (Box 12)
      - Slide Box 5 (Metcalf Houses)
        - Job 117-89, Fox/Bockenstedt (Box 12)
        - Job 118-89, Gilbert/Verbrugge (II) (Box 12)
        - Job 120-91, Holland (II) (Box 12)
      - Slide Box 6 (Construction)
        - Job 26-56, Woods (Box 12)
        - Job 39-58, Pryor (Box 12)
        - Job 40-58, Campbell (Box 12)
        - Job 64-60, Elliott (Box 12)
        - Job 70-61, Ogden (Box 12)